{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite colour?",
      "answer1": "A) Red",
      "answer2": "B) Green",
      "answer3": "C) Pink",
      "answer4": "D) Royal Blue",
      "correct": "C) Pink"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her biggest discomfort?",
      "answer1": "A) Hugh Spiders",
      "answer2": "B) Heights",
      "answer3": "C) Public Speaking",
      "answer4": "D) Venomous Snakes",
      "correct": "C) Public Speaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite childhood memory?",
      "answer1": "A) Climbing tree to run away from people",
      "answer2": "B) Riding bike",
      "answer3": "C) Spending time with father and mother",
      "answer4": "D) Cooking with father",
      "correct": "D) Cooking with father"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite song?",
      "answer1": "A) Sweet Child o' Mine by Guns N' Roses",
      "answer2": "B) Shape of You by Ed Sheeran",
      "answer3": "C) You'll Never Find by Lou Rawls",
      "answer4": "D) Why I Love You by Major Johnson Finley",
      "correct": "D) Why I Love You by Major Johnson Finley"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her dream vacation destination?",
      "answer1": "A) Paris",
      "answer2": "B) Florida, Miami",
      "answer3": "C) Switzerland",
      "answer4": "D) Mozambique",
      "correct": "A) Paris"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite dessert?",
      "answer1": "A) Chocolate Cake",
      "answer2": "B) Ice Cream",
      "answer3": "C) Cheesecake",
      "answer4": "D) Tiramisu Cake",
      "correct": "D) Tiramisu Cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her biggest pet peeve (annoyance)?",
      "answer1": "A) People chewing loudly",
      "answer2": "B) Messy people",
      "answer3": "C) Drivers who overtake people on the road",
      "answer4": "D) People who don't have public decency",
      "correct": "D) People who don't have public decency"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her biggest fear?",
      "answer1": "A) Losing a loved one",
      "answer2": "B) Being Bedridden",
      "answer3": "C) Separating with loved ones",
      "answer4": "D) Jealousy over close family being close with other people",
      "correct": "C) Separating with loved ones"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her biggest accomplishment?",
      "answer1": "A) Graduating college",
      "answer2": "B) Getting a promotion at work",
      "answer3": "C) Starting a hair saloon ",
      "answer4": "D) Starting a family",
      "correct": "D) Starting a family"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her biggest regret?",
      "answer1": "A) Not travelling more",
      "answer2": "B) Not spending more time with family",
      "answer3": "C) Being a risk-taker",
      "answer4": "D) Getting easily attached with people",
      "correct": "D) Getting easily attached with people"
    }
  ]
}